Guide to the Theodore W. "Ted" Minah Records and Papers,1941-1975 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Articles and Speeches,1941-1975
  - Inplant Food Management Editorial, 1964 Jul (Box 38)
  - Institutions Magazine – Article on Portion Control (By T.Minah), 1954 (Box 38)
  - Institutions/Volume Feeding, 1975 (Box 38)
  - International (Institutional) Food Service Manufacturers Assoc. Award, 1968 (Box 38)
  - Ivy League Conference –F.S.D., 1955 (Box 38)
  - Journal of the American Dietetic Association, 1964 Jan (Box 38)
  - Journal of the American Dietetic Association, 1970 Jun (Box 38)
  - Lecture to Dietetic Interns, 1968-1970 (Box 39)
  - Lions Club Speech, 1966 May 18 & 1972 Sep 6 (Box 39)
  - Management as a Function of Dietetics Speech, 1965 Feb 3-4 (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, 1970-1971 (Box 39)
  - NACUFS – First Distinguished Service Award, 1967 May (Box 39)
  - NACUFS – President, 1964 (Box 39)
  - NACUFS Award – T.W. Minah Distinguished Services Award, 1973 (Box 39)
  - NAEB – Raleigh, 1960 (Box 39)
  - National Hotel Exposition, 1963 Nov 11-14 (Box 39)
  - National Restaurant Association Speech, 1948 (Box 39)
  - N.C. Dietetic Assn, 1965 Feb 3-4 (Box 39)
  - N.C. Dietetic Assn – Employee Training, 1962 May 4 (Box 39)
  - N.C. Dietetic Assn – Training the Non-Professional Employee, 1955 Apr 22 (Box 39)
  - N.C.H. – FSI (North Carolina Hospital Food Service Institute), 1966 (Box 39)
  - N.C. Health Dept. – Supervision: How We Work Through People, 1958 Mar 20 (Box 39)
  - N.C. Hotel Assn. Speech, 1953 Dec 4 (Box 39)
  - N.C. Restaurant Association Conference, 1968 Sep (Box 39)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina Restaurant Assn., 1963 (Box 39)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa, 1965-1967 (Box 40)
  - Prices – Comparison of, undated (Box 40)
  - Quality Standards and Food Merchandising for Food Address, 1948 Apr 14 (Box 40)
  - [The] Raleigh Times, 1970 Mar (Box 40)
  - Retirement Articles, 1974-1975 (Box 40)
  - SACUBO (The Southern Association of College and University Business Officers), 1956 (Box 40)
  - SACUBO, 1965 (Box 40)
  - SACUBO – N.C. State, 1954 Apr 30 (Box 40)
  - SACUBO Talk – Atlanta, 1949 (Box 40)
  - School & College Feeding, 1963 Oct (Box 40)
  - School & College Feeding, 1964 Jan (Box 40)
  - School & College Feeding, 1964 May (Box 40)
  - Speech – Costs Can Be Controlled Talk – AHA, 1956 Mar 15 (Box 40)
  - Speech – Durham Restaurant Assn – Cleanliness is Next to Godliness, 1947 (Box 40)
  - Speech – North Carolina Restaurant Association, 1963 Sep 23 (Box 40)
  - Speech – The Role of the Food Service in Higher Education, NACUFS Regional Meeting, Grand Forks, ND, 1964 (Box 40)
  - Woman’s College – Institutions Magazine – Contest, 1955 (Box 40)
- Correspondence,1945-1974 and undated
  8.3 ln. ft. (about 6,200 items)
  This series contains a mixture of business and personal correspondence, postcards, holiday cards, and invitations written to and by Ted Minah. Business correspondence primarily focuses on dining hall operations, employee recommendations, compliments and complaints about dining halls, and other institutions seeking advice from Ted Minah. Personal correspondence includes personal requests from students seeking employment, letters and postcards from former student workers, and personal thank you letters, including several from former Duke University Presidents and Deans. The series is arranged alphabetically and includes a miscellaneous folder for each letter of the alphabet (i.e., Miscellaneous A).
  - Applications for Student Workers, 1945 (Box 41)
  - Atlantic City, 1949 (Box 41)
  - ATO Dinner (Box 41)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous A (Box 41)
  - Bain, Richard C. (Box 41)
  - Ball, Margaret (Dean, Woman’s College) (Box 41)
  - Bennett, Mrs. Mae (Box 41)
  - Berrier, Paul (Box 41)
  - Bersebach, Fred G. (Box 41)
  - Bethke, Miss Lucille (Box 41)
  - Bevier, Ralph H., 1956-1959 (Box 41)
  - Bindewald, Richard (Box 41)
  - Blackburn, John (Chancellor) (Box 41)
  - Blue Jeans (Box 41)
  - Brinkely, Florence (Dean) (Box 41)
  - Brower, Mr. A.S. (Box 41)
  - Bryson, E.C. (Box 41)
  - Correspondence – BA through BL (Box 42)
  - Correspondence – BL through BU, 1957-1959 (Box 42)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous B (Box 42)
  - Carland, Mary (Box 42)
  - Carr (Lynch), Sarah Ann (Box 42)
  - Cato, Philip Carlyle (Box 42)
  - Children’s Home, 1959-1963 (Box 42)
  - Clyde, Pauline, 1959 (Box 42)
  - Connor, Elizabeth May (Box 42)
  - Cooksey, W.H. (Box 42)
  - Coffee Shop, 1945 (Box 42)
  - College & University F.S.D. (Food Service Directors), 1948-1949 (Box 42)
  - Complaints & Compliments, 1945-1949 (Box 42)
  - Compliments and Criticisms, 1967-1971 (Box 42)
  - Coombs, Jack (Box 42)
  - Cox, Diane Martin (Box 42)
  - Cox, Robert B. (Dean) (Box 42)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous C (Box 42)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous C (Box 43)
  - Davidson, Mr. Loren (Box 43)
  - DeYoe, Marguerite (Box 43)
  - DeLong, Mrs. Ann (Box 43)
  - Denby, Mrs. Jane Colclesser (Box 43)
  - Donaldson, Mrs. Margaret Packard (Box 43)
  - Dozier, John, 1961-1964 (Box 43)
  - Dube, Mrs. E.R. (letter to Duke Alumni Register), 1974 Oct (Box 43)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous D (Box 43)
  - Eames, David B., 1957-1959 (Box 43)
  - Edens, Arthur H. (President), 1954-1960 (Box 43)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous E (Box 43)
  - Ferguson, John (Box 44)
  - Ferrell, W.E. (Box 44)
  - Financial Aid Program (Box 44)
  - Food Cost Control – Lectures (Box 44)
  - Food Services Directors (Box 44)
  - Freeman, D.C. (Broken Tooth), 1959 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous F (Box 44)
  - Gibson, Alex (Box 44)
  - Glee Clubs (Box 44)
  - Goldsmith, Alice Elaine (Box 44)
  - Graham, Bert W. (Box 44)
  - Greyhound & Gulf Transport, 1957-1958 (Box 44)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous G (Box 44)
  - Harper, Andrew (Box 44)
  - Hart, Dr. Deryl (President) (Box 44)
  - Henrickson, G.C. (Box 44)
  - Herman, Harold W. (Box 44)
  - Hobbs, Dr. Marcus E. (Box 44)
  - Hopkins, Dr. Everett H. (Vice President) (Box 44)
  - Howard, Mike (Box 44)
  - Howard, W.K. (Box 44)
  - Howe, Isabelle (Gibbs) (Box 44)
  - Hutcheson, Mrs. James (Box 44)
  - Hyde, Lucille (Box 44)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous H (Box 45)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous H (Box 45)
  - International Steward and Caterers’ Association (Box 45)
  - Invitation – Association of Universities of the British Commonwealth (Box 45)
  - Ives, Anne – Insurance Checks (Box 45)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous I (Box 45)
  - Jones, William Bill (Box 45)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous J (Box 45)
  - Kaiser, Elizabeth (Box 45)
  - Keever, Gene (Box 45)
  - Kennedy, Mrs. June (Box 45)
  - Kiwanis Club of Durham, Inc. – Resignation of T.W. Minah (Box 45)
  - Knight, Douglas M. (President) (Box 45)
  - Krahler and Krukin, Inc. – Correspondence & Blueprints (Box 45)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous K (Box 46)
  - Labor Report, 1957 (Box 46)
  - Lance, Inc., 1958 (Box 46)
  - Lee, Willie Earl (Box 46)
  - Lewis, Miss Lou (Box 46)
  - Linke, William R. (Box 46)
  - Lobsters (Box 46)
  - Long, Morris (Box 46)
  - Luckey, Alice Young (Box 46)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous L (Box 46)
  - Malloy, John W. (Box 46)
  - Manchester, Alan (Box 46)
  - Memoranda – All Concerned (Box 46)
  - Mendenhall, Dr. (Survey Reports) (Box 46)
  - Messmer, Terry (Box 46)
  - Miles, Al (Box 46)
  - Miller, W. James (Box 46)
  - Mock, Odell C. (Box 46)
  - Murray College (Box 46)
  - Murray, Mrs. Wintress Dalby (Box 46)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous M (Box 46)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous M (Box 47)
  - N.R.O.T.C. Coffee Mess, 1945 (Box 47)
  - N.R.O.T.C. Recruitment Program (Box 47)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous “N” (Box 47)
  - On-the-Job-Training Program (for Veterans), 1946-1950 (Box 47)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous “O” (Box 47)
  - Park, Daniel J. (Box 47)
  - Parrish, Cynthia (Box 47)
  - Parsons, Donald T. (Box 47)
  - Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 47)
  - P.W.’s (Box 47)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous P (Box 48)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous P (Box 48)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous Q (Box 48)
  - Radcliffe, Mrs. Charles (Box 48)
  - Raleigh, W.A. (Box 48)
  - Ramsauer, Ed (Box 48)
  - Research Triangle Committee (Box 48)
  - Retirement – Letters and Articles, 1974 Jan (Box 48)
  - Reyle, Bruce (Box 48)
  - Ripley, Helen (Box 48)
  - Robinson, George (Box 48)
  - Rogers, Russell (Box 48)
  - Rosenberg, John (Box 48)
  - Rossin, Philip (Box 48)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous R (Box 48)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous R (Box 49)
  - Sanford, Terry (President) (Box 49)
  - Schettler, Vera (Box 49)
  - School and College Feeding (Box 49)
  - Shaffer, Stephen (Box 49)
  - Shaw, Milton (Cornell) (Box 49)
  - Simmons, Vera (Box 49)
  - Smitley, Glen (Box 49)
  - Stafford, Mrs. W.R. Jo (Box 49)
  - Stein, Gary S. (Box 49)
  - Sugar Ration (Box 49)
  - Suggestion Box, 1945 (Box 49)
  - Surplus Property (Box 49)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous S (Box 49)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous S (Box 49)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous S (Box 50)
  - Taylor, David (Box 50)
  - Taylor, Mrs. Elizabeth Dineen (Box 50)
  - [John R.] Thompson Company Correspondence (Box 50)
  - Thompson, Leo C. (Box 50)
  - Tours (Box 50)
  - Training Tables, 1946 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous T (Box 50)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous T (Box 50)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1956-1960 (Box 50)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous U (Box 50)
  - Vacations (Staff) (Box 50)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous V (Box 50)
  - Wall, George Frank (Box 50)
  - Ward, Jim (University Architect) (Box 50)
  - Ward, Larry (Box 50)
  - Webber, John (Box 51)
  - Wellons, Marcie D. (Box 51)
  - West Campus (Box 51)
  - Whitener, Fred (Box 51)
  - Whitford, W.E. (Box 51)
  - Williams, Travis (Box 51)
  - Wilson, Mary Grace (Dean of Woman’s College) (Box 51)
  - Winson, Edward M. (Box 51)
  - Witherspoon, Loy (Box 51)
  - Woollen, Thomas H. (Career Opportunities T.V. Programs) (Box 51)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous W (Box 51)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous W (Box 51)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous W (Box 51)
  - YMCA (Box 51)
  - YMCA – Harriet Tubman Branch (United Fund Committee) (Box 51)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous Y (Box 51)
  - Correspondence – Miscellaneous Z (Box 51)